static:
  title: "Christmas Quiz"
  intro: "Answer a series of Christmas questions to receive a present from Santa ðŸŽ…"
  outro: "Congrats, you answered all questions right! Claim your prize below ðŸŽ‰"
  prize-link: "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ItGkqRcJFRQ"
  quiz-items:
    - id: 1
      question: "How many ghosts show up in A Christmas Carol?"
      answers:
        - "Four"
        - "4"
    - id: 2
      question: "Is Die Hard a Christmas movie?"
      answers:
        - "Yes"
    - id: 3
      question: "What are you supposed to do when you find yourself under the mistletoe?"
      answers:
        - "Kiss"
    - id: 4
      question: "Which country started the tradition of putting up a Christmas tree?"
      answers:
        - "Germany"
    - id: 5
      question: "What was the first company that used Santa Claus in advertising?"
      answers:
        - "Coca-Cola"
        - "Coca Cola"
        - "Cola"
    - id: 6
      question: "How old is Kevin McCallister in Home Alone?"
      answers:
        - "Eight"
        - "8"
    - id: 7
      question: "What is the name of the little girl who befriends the Grinch in the 2000 film?"
      answers:
        - "Cindy Lou Who"
        - "Cindy Lou"
        - "Cindy"
    - id: 8
      question: "What is the name of Kristoff's reindeer in Frozen?"
      answers:
        - "Sven"
    - id: 9
      question: "Which famous Christmas song includes the lyrics: Dashing through the snow, in a one-horse open sleigh?"
      answers:
        - "Jingle Bells"
    - id: 10
      question: "Which TV family has a pet dog called Santaâ€™s Little Helper?"
      answers:
        - "The Simpsons"
        - "Simpsons"